recipe-select.net 2016-01-28

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers the manner in which Picella Ltd. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the enewsstandonline.com. We want you to feel safe online. In line with that policy, we want to let you know how we treat personal information. Personal information is information about you that is personally recognizable like your name, address, email address, or phone/fax number. Picella Ltd. Privacy Policy applies only to Web sites and services that are owned and operated by Picella Ltd. When linking from Picella Ltd. to other Web sites, if you have privacy concerns, we recommend you to review the privacy policies of those sites. It’s also important to note that this Privacy Policy does not pertain to information that you post, yourself.  
Changes to This Privacy Policy  
Picella Ltd. has the discretion to change Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to be informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically.  
Questions and Suggestions  
If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, please complete a feedback form.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
